https://www.magicwicca.com/privacy-policy.html

Log In or Register Change Currency: USD Change Language: Advanced SearchHomePrivacy PolicyShop by CategoryHomepageMagic Dust and Eye PillowsSalts and RootsTarot CardsAthamesCandlesHoly Death CandlesFigure Cermonial Candles7 Day Prepared and Scented Cermonial Candles7 Day Cermonial Candles in Glass14 Day Cermonial Candles in GlassPalm Oil, Pull Out and assorted jar CandlesTapers, Household and PilarVotives and TealightsHolders and AccessoriesOilsAnna Riva Cermonial Anointing OilAbre Melin thru BusinessCaliphs Beloved thru Drive Away EvilEarth thru Good TimesH and H thru KyphiLa Flamme thru NutmegOrange thru Run Devil RunSaffron thru Tutti FruttiUncrossing thru Zula Zula7 Sisters Spiritual Cermonial Anointing OilsSpiritual Cermonial Anointing OilsMulti Oro Pure Cermonial Anointing OilsBody Oils with PheromonesEssential Cermonial Anointing OilsMISCELLANEOUS Cermonial OilsPsychic Cermonial OilDiffusersSpiritual SpraysMistic SpraysIndio SpraysColognes, Perfumes, SoapsSoapsColognesSpiritual PerfumesMulti Oro PerfumesSpiritual Waters, Washes and BathesSpiritual BathsSpiritual Bath and Floor WashesBath SaltsSpiritual WatersTalismansLibros in EspanolPendants and MedalsRitual ItemsWriting MaterialsVoodoo DollsSalts, Roots, Extracts hard to find itemsSanteriaBooksDreams and LotteryBooks # thru BBooks C thru EBooks F thru LBooks M thru PBooks Q thru ZSACHET POWDERS IN ENVELOPECauldronsDecorativeCooking CauldronsCrystal, Acrylic and Therapy BallsCrystal BallsAcrylic BallsHealth Therapy BallsIncenseConesStickPowderArjax Powder Incense 15ozAnna Riva Powder IncensePowerful Indian Powder IncenseResin Gum IncensePowder Incense in EnvelopesBenedictum Powder IncenseHolders, Burners, CharcoalSpiritual KitsCloth Bags and Mojo BagsCloth BagsAlter SuppliesChalices and Scrying BowlsBells, Boxes WandsBesoms, Alter Tiles and ClothsMortar and PestalMailing ListEnter your e-mail address to receive our newsletterYour Shopping BasketYour basket is empty.Featured ProductAir Bath Salts (1#) Glass JarBest SellersKAREN LARA Y SU MAGIA BLANCA7 AFRICAN POWERSWitches Guide to Faery Folk by Edain McCoyJINX STOPPERBody Oil Sex Only With MeBody Oil Mr. Money / Don DineroCome to Me For Him Ven a Mi1382 Size 3 Flat-BottomPrivacy PolicyThe Magick Wicca Privacy Statement At The Magick Wicca, we take your right to privacy very seriously. Our privacy policy is as follows:
All Credit Card and On Line Draft information is secured on Secure Servers and is additionally Encrypted using PGP key coding. The information received is restricted to one computer and is not available to any unauthorized employee to prevent the possibility of Credit Card fraud.
Unless stated otherwise, as in the case of prize drawings, giveaways, and special promotions, we never sell, give, lend, show, or otherwise share any information about our clients or visitors to our web site.
The Magick Wicca does not share general demographic information about our clients as a group with our partners.
The Magick Wicca DOES NOT share or sell your registration information to anyone outside of the company. All registration information is kept private.
If you have any concerns about our privacy policy, please contact us:  About UsContact UsTerms & ConditionsPrivacy PolicyContact Uskuroutohttps://www.magicwicca.comcommonMobile SiteeCommerce by CubeCart
